[
  {
    "id": "bbasdfjlhlajsdf",
    "title": "Python Quizz Module",
    "count": 10,
    "timeLimit": "Unlimited",
    "difficulty": "Easy",
    "questions": [
      {
        "id": 1,
        "question": "print type(type(int))",
        "options": ["type 'int'", "type 'type'", "Error", "0"],
        "correctAnswer": "type 'type'"
      },
      {
        "id": 2,
        "question": "L = ['a','b','c','d'] print ''.join(L)",
        "options": ["Error", "None", "abcd", "['a','b','c','d']"],
        "correctAnswer": "abcd"
      },
      {
        "id": 3,
        "question": "chr(ord('A'))",
        "options": ["A", "B", "a", "Error"],
        "correctAnswer": "A"
      },
      {
        "id": 4,
        "question": "What is the output of the following program :y = 8 z = lambda x : x * y print z(6)",
        "options": ["48", "14", "64", "None of the above"],
        "correctAnswer": "48"
      },
      {
        "id": 5,
        "question": "What is called when a function is defined inside a class?",
        "options": ["Module", "Class", "Another Function", "Method"],
        "correctAnswer": "Method"
      },
      {
        "id": 6,
        "question": "Which of the following is the use of id() function in python?",
        "options": [
          "Id returns the identity of the object",
          "Every object doesnâ€™t have a unique id",
          "All of the mentioned",
          "None of the mentioned"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "Id returns the identity of the object"
      },
      {
        "id": 7,
        "question": "Suppose list1 is [3, 4, 5, 20, 5, 25, 1, 3], what is list1 after list1.pop(1)?",
        "options": [
          "[3, 4, 5, 20, 5, 25, 1, 3]",
          "[1, 3, 3, 4, 5, 5, 20, 25]",
          "[3, 5, 20, 5, 25, 1, 3]",
          "[1, 3, 4, 5, 20, 5, 25]"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "[3, 5, 20, 5, 25, 1, 3]"
      },
      {
        "id": 8,
        "question": "Which of the following is the use of id() function in python?",
        "options": [
          "the current time in milliseconds since midnight, January 1, 1970 GMT (the Unix time)",
          "the current time in milliseconds",
          "the current time",
          "the current time in milliseconds since midnight, January 1, 1970"
        ],
        "correctAnswer": "the current time in milliseconds since midnight, January 1, 1970 GMT (the Unix time)"
      },
      {
        "id": 9,
        "question": "Which of these is not a core data type?",
        "options": ["Lists", "Dictionary", "Tuples", "Class"],
        "correctAnswer": "Class"
      },
      {
        "id": 10,
        "question": "Which of the following function convert a string to a float in python?",
        "options": ["int(x [,base])", "long(x [,base] )", "float(x)", "str(x)"],
        "correctAnswer": "float(x)"
      }
    ]
  }
]
